Sophie.
Do you think you could
persuade your sister
to make at least
a token appearance?
I doubt it.
Please try.
- Sure, mom.
- Okay.
Oh, how are you?
Good to see you.
My condolences.
Abs?
Abby, are you awake?
- Okay, go ahead.
- Yeah, I'm on my way.
Yeah.
All right. All right.
I'm heading through
the front entrance right now.
What's your 20?
Hey, boss.
Victim's name is Austin Marr.
23. Multiple stab wounds.
Killed in the guesthouse
last night around 2:00 A.M.
What's with all the security?
Well, the house belongs
to a federal judge
named Pauline Fitzwilliam.
Her mother just died.
A lot of VIPs are here for the wake.
- Stiff security for a wake.
- Where's Jane?
Who knows? He can catch up
when he gets here.
Metal items
in the plastic container, please
I was looking for Abby.
I didn't even know
Austin was in the house.
- He doesn't live here?
- No.
He's Abby's boyfriend.
He's sweet and gentle.
Who would do this to him?
I need you to stay with me, Sophie.
Okay.
Does Austin have family
in the area?
No.
Sophie, do you know
where Austin works?
I'm not sure. He's...
He's an illustrator
for children's books.
And how was
his relationship with Abby?
They were in love.
Austin treated her like gold.
When was the last time
you saw your sister?
Yesterday afternoon.
Where is she?
What's happened to her?
That's what we're trying
to figure out.
We'll let you know as soon
as we find anything out.
- Thank you for your time.
- But she's okay, right?
'Cause she's my baby sister.
- We'll let you know.
- Okay.
I talked to security.
They say they've got a sealed
perimeter around the estate.
No one goes in or out
unless it's through them.
Abby came in yesterday morning
at 8:40, but there's no record
that she left.
So she's still in the house?
That's the thing. Local PD and security
searched the property...
every building, every room.
They can't find her anywhere.
Well, maybe she left
with someone.
Security's saying no.
They check everyone that leaves.
They even search their cars.
So Abby's missing, but security
says she never left?
I was having such a good day.
Cho, check out Austin...
home, work, other friends.
Van Pelt, get with security.
I want the names of everybody
who was on the property at the time
of death, and I wanna talk to 'em.
- On it.
- Uh, and if you see Jane
tell him he's officially tardy.
"Sir, all metals items
in the plastic bin, please."
"Sir, please step back."
Uh, I'm with CBI.
I'm in a hurry.
I'm just gonna go around.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where's your badge?
- You just grabbed my arm.
- Oh, maybe you didn't hear me.
Marcus Whiteside, Security Chief here.
Where's your badge?
- That's my badge.
- Okay, then. Now...
- go through the gate.
- Where's your badge?
- Are we gonna have a problem here?
- No. Not at all. I'm just asking.
Through the gate.
I'm one of the good guys here, man.
I'm... I'm here to help.
Family, friends, CBI... everyone goes
through the gate. Got it?
I got it. That means you go
through the gate, too?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
Marcus, please, be my guest.
After you. The least I could do.
Uh, you know, I-I may...
Can I just... please?
Thank you.
Seems to be working.
"Come on. I want a bite.
Come on. Just give me a bite."
- "No. You don't deserve it."
- "I just want one..."
"Well, maybe I'm just gonna
have to take it then."
"Then take it. No?"
- "I love you so much."
- "I love you, too."
"Oh. You hear that?
She loves me."
I know what's happened here.
What's that, judge?
Three months ago, I sentenced
a man named Raymond Tubbs
to 40 years without parole.
He's a white supremacist
runs a gang
that's been robbing banks
up and down the coast.
Mr. Tubbs swore he would kill me
and my family so obviously...
someone working for him
killed poor Austin
and took Abby.
But your security team says
nobody entered the compound.
Well, they also said
Abby must still be here
and they've searched
and haven't found her
so obviously they're wrong
in some respects.
Where's Tubbs doing time?
Folsom.
That doesn't stop him.
Last month he sent a member of
his gang to break into our house.
That's when we stepped up security.
Did your forensics get anything
from the crime scene?
Ma'am, we prefer not to give
details of our investigation
- until it's compl...
- Agent, I was a DA for 12 years.
I can pick up the phone
and find out what you've got
or you can just tell me.
Partial prints on the murder weapon
and Austin's blood.
- We're running it now.
- Fine.
You'll find that it belongs
to someone working for Tubbs.
You track him, you will find Abby.
We'll look into Tubbs
but there are other avenues
to explore.
Such as?
Ma'am, as a matter of course
we looked
into Abby's background.
She has issues
with drug and alcohol abuse.
Had issues.
She's been clean for months and what
has that to do with this situation?
Parents aren't always the first
to know about a relapse
and drug dealers
are dangerous company.
Abby was clean and sober.
- And Austin?
- He was the same.
And how was
their relationship lately?
It was good.
There were wounds
on his face...
fingernail scratches which suggests
he had a fight with a female
shortly before he was killed.
Are you suggesting
that Abby fought with Austin
and then killed him?
Like I said, ma'am
other avenues to explore.
Agent, if my daughter
comes to harm
because you frittered away
your time
looking into her personal life
your career is over.
Do you understand me?
Ma'am, I understand your distress
during this difficult time
but we'll go wherever
this investigation takes us.
It's my duty.
Ah.
Can I help you?
Well, that depends.
Who are you?
- Ed Saban.
- Uh, I just...
- And you are?
- Patrick Jane, CBI.
Oh, I-I spoke with one
of your colleagues, uh...
Van Pelt, I believe.
Does that mean you've had
enough of questions?
- Uh... No. That... that's not what I...
- Good.
Where were you last night?
Uh... here.
Uh, i-i-in bed. I...
I was tired from working all day
and took a sleeping pill.
Hmm.
I'm not actually a cop.
I'm what you, uh, would refer
to as a...
- consultant.
- Oh.
- Funny.
- No.
You have a distinctly medical air.
Are you a family doctor?
Uh, Ethel's. I, uh, I took care
of her the last year or so.
- Oops.
- Ethel was 93.
I think all things considered
we gave her
a reasonably peaceful end.
So what do you think's
happened to Abby?
Who?
Abigail Fitzwilliam...
Ethel's granddaughter.
Oh, Abby. Yeah.
What about her?
- She's missing, isn't she?
- Is she?
Do the police know?
- You're joking again.
- Yes.
- How would you describe Abby?
- Oh, uh...
A good-hearted young woman.
Full of life. Vivacious.
Oh. Uh, excuse me.
I have a...
Um, please?
Oh.
Lisbon, hello.
Jane, where are you?
I'm just talking
with the family doctor here.
He says our missing girl is an unstable
nymphomaniacal stoner.
- Interesting, no?
- Uh, I didn't say that.
Yes, you did.
You practically screamed it.
I'm at the front door now.
Meet me here.
Yeah. I-I'll be right there.
Thanks for your time.
"No sign of the girl?"
"No, and the security people say she
couldn't have possibly left the property"
"without their knowledge."
We should see if she was sleeping
with any of the security people.
It's a thought. And the mom
says neo-Nazis staged a raid
but security said nobody came
on the property so puzzle that out.
Give me a minute.
Cho. Yeah, I need you
to check out Raymond Tubbs.
He's in federal prison in Folsom.
Yeah, talk to him, see what he knows
about the Fitzwilliams.
Also, did you get anything
on those fingerprints?
Let me know.
Okay. Minute's up.
What's the answer?
That was not a minute. That was...
- less than 30 seconds, even.
- Reasonably
Agent Lisbon, you said that, um...
if you found anything
you'd let me know.
- Have you?
- No, Sophie. I'm sorry.
I got it.
- What?
- You asked me to puzzle it out.
- I puzzled it out.
- What? What is it?
Uh, well, there's been
no ransom demand
so that rules out abduction
leaves three options
for your sister's disappearance.
One, she was killed and her body
was removed from the compound.
Two, she was killed and her body
was hidden on the compound.
Or three, she killed Austin
and fled the scene.
No, that can't be.
You're hiding something.
What? No?
Obviously something
about your sister. What is it?
- No.
- Oh, come on. You can tell me.
You don't know Abby.
She would never hurt Austin.
You wanna believe that but you know
it's not true, don't you?
You ever notice that feeling
that physical unwell feeling
you get
when you know you should say
or do something and you don't?
Heart pounds
headache, backache.
You can feel better...
immediately
if you tell the truth.
Right now.
Yesterday I went to
the guesthouse to see Abby.
Mm-hmm.
Austin was there
and they were arguing.
I have never seen them like that.
Abby tried to leave
and Austin started
to shake her
and he was yelling at her
and shaking her.
What did Abby do?
- She hit him in the face.
- Yeah.
He was bleeding.
Then what happened?
I don't know. I left.
Excuse me.
Of course.
Well, thank you, Sophie.
That was very valuable.
Now you should take
a little lie-down
maybe catch up on some sleep.
Okay.
When you wake up
you're gonna feel a lot better.
Thank you.
Forensics got a match
from the prints
from the knife that was used
as the murder weapon.
They're Abby's.
"I'm telling you, Abby did not leave
that compound."
You and your men searched
the house and the grounds.
She wasn't there?
Is it possible that there's a hole
in the system?
There are cameras, regular patrols,
and motion sensors.
It's just not possible.
We'll have to search
the place again is all.
- We must've missed her.
- First things first
could somebody in the family
have helped Abby escape?
None of them have access
to the security system
not even Pauline.
What about your men?
Are any of them vulnerabilities?
They're ex-military
and law enforcement.
I handpicked them myself.
We're gonna need a list
of their names.
You're wasting your time.
You should be talking
to all the people
who were on the compound
when Austin was killed.
We have talked to them.
Six in total, not including Abby...
Pauline, Sophie, Ed Saban
two maids, Ethel's cousin Ruth.
We're looking into all of them
but right now
what I am interested in
is finding Abby.
So Abby and Austin
have a fight
and then later on
that night, she kills him?
That's what it looks like.
Still doesn't explain
how she got off the estate.
When we find Abby
we'll have our answer.
Whiteside sent me a list
of the names of his security team.
Run background checks on them.
See if anything comes up.
- Yeah, you got it.
- Hey, boss.
Abby Fitzwilliam used her credit card
three hours ago at a boutique
in San Francisco.
The store faxed over
an itemized receipt.
Let's go check it out.
"Marin Life" magazine?
It's a good read.
Abby liked to party
just like the doctor said.
She and her posse
are all through this.
- The point is...
- I'm exploring the world of the suspect.
Well, you enjoy exploring.
We'll go get on her trail
and arrest her.
- What did Abby buy at the store?
- Um...
skirt suit, blazer
and a Tumi bag. Why?
No reason.
She was in a few hours ago.
- Okay...
- She spent $800
on a skirt suit
blazer, and a handbag.
- Okay...
- Here's her picture.
Oh, yeah. I remember.
Blonder, though.
- Was she with anyone?
- No.
Do you remember
anything else about her?
Fierce shoes.
Oh! She left an address.
Jacket needed altering.
Do you want it?
Yes.
Put your badge away. If she thinks
we're cops she might run.
I don't feel like running.
Hi. We have
a delivery from L Couturier.
- You wanna open the door?
- "She's lying."
- Abby Fitzwilliam, you're under arrest.
- I'm not Abby.
Put your hands in the air now!
Lisbon, Grace
where's your manners?
This is Daniella,
Abby's best friend.
Come in. Have a seat.
Okay. You win.
How'd you find Daniella?
What's my prize?
Abby Fitzwilliam is a party girl
with a rebellious streak.
She dresses like one.
Lots of animal prints.
- The receipt.
- Skirt suit, blazer, Tumi bag.
Very east coast prep.
No way Abby would've bought
any of that.
Daniella is the only one
of Abby's friends
with that, uh
appropriate sense of style.
- How'd you find her?
- ESP.
No, I had Cho look up
her address.
Why did you steal
Abby's credit card?
I didn't. She loaned it to me.
She was a good friend.
I have friends, Daniella.
I don't loan them
my credit card.
Well, what can I say?
Abby is generous.
I have a job interview
in a few days.
She said I needed to look
my best.
She always helped me
when I needed it.
Even if I said no
she wouldn't listen.
It's true.
Ask around. She did it
for lots of people.
When did she give you
the card?
Um... three days ago.
The day before she went missing?
Abby called me and told me
her grandma was really sick
and that she wasn't gonna last
much longer.
I went over to be with her.
- How'd she seem?
- She was sad.
Crying a lot.
She and her grandma
were really close.
And she was drinking.
"It was... it was just wine but still."
I told her I didn't think
it was a good idea.
You know, she had problems
with that kinda stuff.
Was Austin there?
No. Abby wouldn't have been
drinking if he was.
Austin's totally straight-edged.
He got her sober.
The night Abby went missing
where were you?
In L.A. for work.
Boss, need you out here.
I said Mr. Jane.
I wanna talk to Mr. Jane.
- Where is he?
- I turned my back for a second.
You know how he is.
He's not here right now, Sophie.
What's the problem?
I, um, I got this message.
I don't know what it means.
What message?
What are you talking about?
"Tell your bitch mom
that's what she gets"
"for messing
with Raymond Tubbs."
"Your sister and her friend
were just the beginning."
"You will reap the whirlwind.
Eight, eight."
I've never heard
that voice before.
"Eight, eight"?
What does that mean?
It's a code used
by white supremacists.
The eighth letter of the alphabet
"HH", "Heil Hitler."
It's blocked. Sophie we're gonna need
your phone for a little while.
- Get a trace on it.
- Yeah, you got it.
You said Abby did this.
You said her fingerprint
was on the knife.
We don't know what this means
but right now
you shouldn't be alone.
I'm gonna have
an agent bring you home.
What about Abby? Did these people
do something to her?
That's what we're gonna find out.
Come with me.
Okay.
Raymond Tubbs?
Yeah. Who are you?
I'm Agent Cho from the CBI.
I'd like to ask you a few questions
about Pauline Fitzwilliam.
What about her?
A man was killed
on the Fitzwilliam compound.
A family member is missing.
Another family member
received a voice mail.
It said, "That's what you get
for messing with Raymond Tubbs."
Leadership's a bitch, huh?
You try to keep your folks
on point
and then some darn fool
opens his mouth.
Where you hail
from Agent Cho?
Oakland.
Okay.
- Where are your parents from?
- Korea.
Koreans. Good people.
Know who they are.
A lotta people today don't know
who the heck they are.
A man without knowledge
of his roots
is like a cabbage
in this society.
That's true.
So you deny any connection
to the incidents
- at the Fitzwilliam compound?
- Heck, no.
There's an Aryan soldier
who honors and respects me
inside the compound. He carried
out the mission for me.
I'm just saying I wouldn't
call anyone about it.
That's just dumb.
But I guess there's
a dummy in any group.
Right, Agent Cho?
- Mr. Jane, may I ask...
- Marcus
if I wanted
to break into this compound
where would be
the best place to do it?
Excuse me?
Where's the weak link?
This property is 100% secure.
When you learned someone had
been murdered in the guesthouse
something popped
into your mind...
an image of a location you've been
worried about, a weakness.
What was it?
- No.
- Yes.
- It's nothing, but, uh...
- Go on.
North wall.
Property bends around a gully.
Curve in the wall makes it
hard for the sensors
to pick up movement.
Okay.
You'll need to go through the gate.
Okay. Of course.
This Aryan soldier...
give me a name.
Yeah. No.
Why would I do that?
You've had your revenge already.
Why not give up your man?
Life could be a lot easier
for you in here
if we tell the warden
you're helping us out.
Extra smokes, more yard time?
Yeah. Like that.
Flat screen TV maybe.
You don't understand.
There's honor among us race warriors.
Loyalty. Brotherhood.
Yeah, right.
What do you mean,
"Yeah, right"?
It means you're wasting my time.
You have no one
inside the compound.
There are no Aryan warriors
out there awaiting your orders.
You're a sad little man
alone in a box
living on delusions of grandeur.
You are 100% wrong.
I got an army behind me.
An army!
And I got a guy inside.
- No, you don't.
- Hey, wait a minute!
Howard Dressler is his name.
My guy. Inside.
So choke on that, Cho.
Thanks.
Heil Hitler.
Blood pressure's still high.
So's your heart rate.
I'm gonna give you a Xanax
to help calm you down.
I don't want any medication.
Not today.
Any word on Abby?
No.
Then if you'll excuse me
my mother's funeral
is this afternoon
and I really need
to finish her eulogy.
- I'll come back later.
- Thank you, Ed.
So you're holding
the service here?
Yes. She's being buried
on the property beside my father.
Surprising you're going ahead with it
given recent events.
What would you have me do,
Mr. Jane?
I'm sorry if I'm not behaving
the way you think I should.
It's not every day my mother dies
and my daughter goes missing.
Now if there's...
anything else you need...
- No.
- Good.
- Because I really must finish this.
- By all means.
Hmm.
That's a beautiful rug.
- Thank you.
- It's very nice. Held up well.
Especially having kids in the house.
That's because I never let
the girls play on it.
You said that
but Abby didn't listen
to you, did she?
No.
Whatever she was told not to do
that's exactly what she would do.
Always contrary.
Hard for someone like you
to handle, I imagine.
Someone like me?
Disciplined. Rigorous.
Wound. You are wound.
It wasn't all bad.
She's a beautiful girl.
She's strong and funny...
and we'd grown apart
these past few years because...
Well, ever since my husband died
but even so there were times
when Abby and I were together
and it was as if
she were a girl again and...
we were happy.
She's dead, isn't she?
My daughter's dead.
It's not unlikely.
Excuse me.
- What's this?
- Visitor logs from the security team...
every person who entered
and left the compound
over the last three months.
Lisbon wants us
to look through 'em.
Raymond Tubbs said he had
a man named Howard Dressler
inside the compound.
Is that new?
Oh. Yes.
- It's a gift?
- Uh-huh.
From O'Laughlin, huh?
Uh-huh.
He has good taste.
Thanks.
What was that name again?
Uh, Howard Dressler.
Got him.
Nice.
- What's up?
- "We found Howard Dressler."
"He tried to run
but we caught him."
"We're gonna take him in
now for questioning."
Nice work. I'll call you back.
What's going on?
Perimeter sensor's been tripped.
Someone's trying to break onto
the compound. We're on our way.
CBI!
Don't move!
Turn around slowly
with your hands up.
- Jane?
- Hey, Lisbon.
When did you get here?
Hey, hey, hey.
Jane.
How are you guys doing today?
I, myself...
am having a great day.
I got a call
from a Pauline Fitzwilliam.
A federal judge, Fitzwilliam.
Saying that a CBI consultant
was caught stealing a rug
from her residence.
- Ma'am, I sincerely apologize...
- Oh, hush, Lisbon.
There's no reason to apologize.
I was working the case.
The rug was a stand-in corpse.
I just wanted to see
if it was possible for the killer
to leave the compound
with Abby's body.
And is it possible?
Not unless the culprit
was a mountain gorilla.
So now you've had your fun
to no useful end
and now she's asking me
to remove you from the case.
Is there any reason
why I shouldn't do as she asks?
She's a suspect.
Really?
She hasn't been excluded
has she?
Then she's still a suspect
and it would look bad to be seen
allowing a murder suspect
dictate the terms
of an investigation
right?
Is this true, Lisbon?
Is she a suspect?
She has not been excluded.
Okay.
I'll give you some more rope.
Don't hang yourself with it.
And, you know
next time call me
when you wanna do
some more foolishness.
"Foolishness," I think
is a little harsh...
- Go.
- Okay, I'm leaving.
I have your numbers.
Come on, Howard.
Don't lie to me.
Already spoke to Raymond Tubbs.
Raymond Tubbs?
- What about him?
- Well, you tell me.
He's an American patriot.
I subscribe
to some of his newsletters.
There's no crime in that.
Well, Tubbs says you're his guy
inside the Fitzwilliam compound.
Says that you're the, uh...
"Aryan warrior that avenged
his unjust imprisonment"
- killed Austin Marr.
- Whoa. I had nothing to do with that.
Okay. If you say so.
But you can see how it looks.
Not good.
No, no, no. I keep my business
and my politics totally separate.
Oh, the Third Reich Pool
Cleaning Company
doesn't play so good, huh?
I've exchanged a few
e-mails with Tubbs. That's all.
If he says any different
he's lying.
I got immunity for what
I say in here, right?
No.
Okay. Occasionally...
I got stuff for Abby.
Stuff? You sold her drugs?
A little coke. Some meth.
When was the last time
you scored for her?
Not for a couple of months
but then the other day
she hit me up.
She was in a real bad way.
She asked me for an eight ball
and some downers.
It took me a few days
but I got 'em.
But the morning I showed up
there was cops everywhere.
I didn't even get
to give 'em to her.
Look, I know I screwed up
but I didn't kill Austin.
There was a useful end
by the way.
We now know for sure that nobody
entered or left the property
the night of the murder
so she must've been murdered
in the guest room
along with Austin.
Then the killer hid her body.
We searched.
She's not on the compound.
You searched for a living,
breathing woman
and not a dead body.
Big difference.
Why would the killer hide
one victim
and leave the other one behind?
Good question.
We'll search the property again.
This time we'll get cadaver dogs
and more personnel.
No need. I know exactly
where the body is hidden.
Wait. Wait.
What are you gonna do?
Just talk.
But they're in the middle
of the funeral.
You can't just walk
in there willy-nilly.
- Yeah. That's right.
- Thank you.
- I forgot to call Hightower.
- Hightower? Why?
Voice mail.
Hey, Hightower. It's Jane.
Just wanted to let you know
that, uh, there's gonna be
what you like to call
"foolishness" going on
at Ethel Sebring's funeral.
That's it. Have a great day.
She told me to call.
- Better hurry.
- Jane.
Jane.
God, our father
your power brings us to birth.
Your Providence guides
our lives
and by your command
we return to dust.
Unite us together in one family
to sing your praise forever
and ever. Amen.
In the name of the father
and of the son
and of the holy spirit, amen.
Amen. Thank you, father.
Uh, good afternoon
ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Patrick Jane.
For those of you
who don't know me
I am a consultant with the CBI.
I know that you're all here today
to mourn the loss of Ethel Sebring
but I have a very important announcement
- that simply can't wait.
- What is the meaning of this?
Uh, just bear with me
please, for one moment.
Well, there's no easy way
to say this
so I'm just gonna
come straight out with it.
Abby Fitzwilliam is dead.
No.
Yeah, it's true, Sophie.
I'm... I'm very sorry for your loss.
How?
We don't know all the details
as yet
but we will know very soon.
Where is she?
She's hidden
in your grandmother's casket.
It's quite clever, actually. It's... it's
one place you wouldn't look for a body
other than the obvious
exception, of course.
Are you playing
some sort of demented joke?
I wish I could say I was.
Uh...
They were both small women.
They could fit comfortably
together in this box.
The only way we can tell for sure
is if we, uh...
Well, we're gonna have to take
a quick peek.
Um, we... we will do it inside.
Dr. Saban will oversee proceedings
to make sure
that everything is shipshape.
Agent, have you no control
over this buffoon?
Lisbon, trust me.
You gotta trust me on this one.
Mr. Jane is making
a valid point.
Ma'am, you know more
about the law than we do.
We can get a warrant but...
I think this will be quicker
and less intrusive
with all due respect.
This is wrong.
- Oh, please.
- Ethel was dignified in life.
She'd want to remain so
in death.
Doctor, you of all people should know
there's nothing dignified about death.
What's going on?
Oh.
- You got my message.
- Ma'am, everything is under control.
- What's he doing to that casket?
- Well, that's what I was calling you about.
Opening it? Jane says
that Abby Fitzwilliam's body
is in the casket.
Oh, my God.
Have you gone completely insane?
No, I don't think so.
There we go.
Pauline, are you sure
you wanna do this?
Just get it over with.
What?
Oh.
Oh, no.
The guests have been sent home.
The funeral's been postponed.
- I hope you're happy.
- Oh, it doesn't make sense.
Abby's body is not in this coffin.
You promised me.
Yeah, I thought she was.
I was certain that she was in there.
Well, you were wrong.
Well, it doesn't make sense
that I was wrong.
Stop saying that!
But this is the perfect place
to hide the body.
It's the one place
that no one would think to look.
Jane, that's enough.
No, w... she's on this compound.
I know that.
- I know that she's on this compound.
- Jane.
We need to get the sniffer dogs
and the helicopters and...
'cause she is here.
I am so sorry.
Sorry.
Okay. All right.
Um...
At first light tomorrow
I want you to start a comprehensive
search for Abby's body.
If she's here, find her.
She's here.
Lisbon, what were you thinking?
I was... no excuses, ma'am.
He asked me to trust him
and I did.
Your job is not to trust him.
Your job is to trust
your judgment, not his.
That poor woman
was in the ground.
Not in the ground
but on her way.
I mean, aren't we all on our way?
You have messed with the funeral
of a high court judge's mother
on the very day she finds out
that her daughter is most likely dead.
That is a very bad career move
for all of us.
Sorry if I got you guys into trouble.
I made a mistake.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Say that again.
I made a mistake. I said it twice.
I won't say it again.
Because it just now occurs to me
that perhaps I'll be proven not quite
as wrong as I appear to be
- in this very moment.
- Is that right?
Yes. In fact, I'm sure of it.
So don't worry.
Your careers are safe.
Judge Fitzwilliam will change her tune
once I reveal her daughter's killer.
Won't she?
I imagine she will.
When do you plan on doing that?
- This very evening.
- This very night?
But you have to trust me.
Right. And what if you're wrong again?
Well, if I'm wrong
then we're in deep trouble.
But what are the chances, really
of me being wrong
twice in a row?
Think about that one.
Of course, if either of you
have a better idea
how to find Abby's body
and catch her killer, please.
These are not taxi doors,
they're ears.
It's not gonna work
unless you're quiet.
I can't keep quiet.
My legs are asleep.
What do you mean
your legs are asleep?
Legs don't sleep.
It's absurd. I don't know
why people say that.
Damn.
Where the hell is it?
Hello?
"What's up, Doc?"
Put your hands in the air!
Sorry.
Did we scare you?
You hid Abby's body, and not Austin's
because you had to.
Evidence of your guilt
was inside Abby.
Come on. We both know
the autopsy will confirm it.
You were giving Abby drugs.
A few days before Ethel died
"Abby relapsed."
"She was an addict."
She was either gonna get her drugs
from me or from the street.
"I was managing her addiction."
"It's recognized
therapeutic practice."
For which you were paid.
Well, yes, of course.
I'm a doctor.
"Of course. So you weren't
doing it to help Abby out."
You were doing it
for the money.
With Ethel dying, you needed
a new source of income.
"Then along came Abby
a rich, young addict."
"Abby, it's okay.
You're okay."
"You're okay. Abby.
Abby, stay with me. Abby."
"Abby. Abby, stay with me."
She OD'd so fast.
I couldn't save her.
Austin came back.
- "What's going on?"
- "Saw what had happened."
"What... what'd you do to her?"
He was gonna go to the police.
Turn me in.
My whole life was over
if he made that call.
I picked up the knife
"just to stop him
not to hurt him."
"I wasn't thinking."
I figured if I made it look
like Abby did it...
"people would believe it."
I knew if they found Abby's body
they'd find the drugs in her system.
So I hid her in my room
in the closet.
I was so scared when the police
came to search the house.
I was sure they'd find her.
You took advantage of Abby.
She trusted you
and you preyed on her
in her weakest moment.
She never had a chance.
- Hey.
- Mm?
So I just talked
to Judge Fitzwilliam.
- And?
- And she says
that if you will apologize
for the cavalier manner
with which you disrupted
her mother's burial
she will not pursue
disciplinary action against you
or Lisbon or myself.
Hmm. Tell her Jane says
she's a self-righteous
embittered old bat
- and she should thank me.
- Oh, God, Jane, please.
You're right, Mr. Jane.
I came here for an apology
but I realize now I was wrong
to stand on my dignity.
I am embittered.
And your arrogant, callous
juvenile behavior
did reveal the truth after all
so...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- Good evening to you.
- Good evening.
Sorry.
Okay, then.
Everyone's happy.